[
  {
    "question": "What temperature does water boil at?",
    "answers": [
      "50 degrees Celcius",
      "25 degrees Celcius",
      "100 degrees Celcius",
      "150 degrees Celcius"
    ],
    "correct": "100 degrees Celcius"
  },

  {
    "question": "When an hausa man marries a Yoruba woman, we call it ______________marriage",
    "answers": ["Intra-ethnic", "Ethnic", "Inter-ethnic", "Wedding"],
    "correct": "Inter-ethnic"
  },

  {
    "question": "_____________ colonized Nigeria",
    "answers": ["Italy", "Ghana", "Britian", "America"],
    "correct": "Britian"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
    "answers": ["Dog", "Elephant", "Goat", "Lion"],
    "correct": "Elephant"
  },

  {
    "question": "Nigeria got her independence on __________________",
    "answers": [
      "October  1st 1960",
      "October 1st 1860",
      "October 1st 1760",
      "October 1st 1660"
    ],
    "correct": "October  1st 1960"
  },

  {
    "question": "What colour is a panda?",
    "answers": [
      "Green and Yellow",
      "Blue and Red",
      "Green and White",
      "Black and White"
    ],
    "correct": "Black and White"
  },

  {
    "question": "Where is the smallest bone in the human body?",
    "answers": ["The Chest", "The Ear", "The Legs", "The Hands"],
    "correct": "The Ear"
  },

  {
    "question": "What does the roman numeral C represent?",
    "answers": ["100", "10", "10,000", "1,000,000"],
    "correct": "100"
  },

  {
    "question": "Christianity introduced ______________ ",
    "answers": ["Monogamy", "Polygamy", "Large", "Extended"],
    "correct": "Monogamy"
  },

  {
    "question": "Inter-ethnic marriage is between couples from different __________ group.",
    "answers": ["Religion", "Family", "School", "Ethnic"],
    "correct": "Ethnic"
  },

  {
    "question": "What’s the most important book in the Moslem religion?",
    "answers": [
      "The Koran",
      "The Dictionary",
      "The Bible",
      "The Chemistry text Book"
    ],
    "correct": "The Koran"
  },

  {
    "question": "What’s the capital of Ethiopia?",
    "answers": ["Cape Town", "San Francisco", "Addis Ababa", "Syndey"],
    "correct": "Addis Ababa"
  },

  {
    "question": "How many squares are there on a chess board?",
    "answers": ["128", "64", "32", "256"],
    "correct": "64"
  },

  {
    "question": "Marriage takes place in the following place except _______",
    "answers": ["Hospital", "Church", "Mosque", "Traditional"],
    "correct": "Hospital"
  },

  {
    "question": "What are the first three words of the bible?",
    "answers": [
      "be with everyone",
      "Again Jesus asked",
      "In the beginning",
      "At that time"
    ],
    "correct": "In the beginning"
  },

  {
    "question": "The award of honour is given by the  ___________of a country.",
    "answers": ["Governor", "Minister", "President", "Senator"],
    "correct": "President"
  },

  {
    "question": "Tolerance is an act of _______________.",
    "answers": ["Disagreement", "Fighthing", "Lying", "Endurance"],
    "correct": "Endurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "___________security management is the means by which a person ensure adequate security of himself",
    "answers": ["Individual", "Social", "Relationship", "Personal"],
    "correct": "Personal"
  },

  {
    "question": "Any action that is morally wrong is known as_______________",
    "answers": ["Punishment", "Crime", "Penalty", "Suicide"],
    "correct": "Crime"
  },
  {
    "question": "A pain that somebody is made to suffer because he/she committed a crime is known as ____________",
    "answers": ["Attitude", "Punishment", "Control", "Insult"],
    "correct": "Punishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fake drugs includes drug that are not ____________",
    "answers": ["Genuine", "Grinded", "Coloured", "Imported"],
    "correct": "Genuine"
  },
  {
    "question": "_______________is the act of taking or stealing somebody’s property",
    "answers": ["Forgery", "Rape", "Theft", "Fraud"],
    "correct": "Theft"
  },

  {
    "question": "The highest national honour award in Nigeria is ______________",
    "answers": ["CFR", "CON", "CFU", "GCON"],
    "correct": "GCON"
  },
  {
    "question": "Union between a man and a woman to ______ together as husband and wife is called marriage.",
    "answers": ["Life", "Die", "Live", "Leave"],
    "correct": "Live"
  },

  {
    "question": "An award given to somebody  who has contributed to national development is known as__________",
    "answers": [
      "National Award",
      "Country Award",
      "State Award",
      "Presidental Award"
    ],
    "correct": "National Award"
  }
]
